let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'console.log()' statement in JavaScript?",
    answer: "To print output to the console",
    options: [
      "To declare a variable",
      "To create a loop",
      "To print output to the console",
      "To define a function"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which programming language is known for its use in web development and can be run in the browser?",
    answer: "JavaScript",
    options: [
      "Java",
      "C++",
      "Python",
      "JavaScript"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    options: [
      "Counter Style Sheets",
      "Computer Style Sheets",
      "Colorful Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the role of 'DOCTYPE' declaration in HTML?",
    answer: "To specify the version of HTML",
    options: [
      "To create a new document",
      "To specify the version of HTML",
      "To link external stylesheets",
      "To define a doctype"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In programming, what does the term 'variable' refer to?",
    answer: "A container for storing data values",
    options: [
      "A mathematical operation",
      "A conditional statement",
      "A container for storing data values",
      "A loop structure"
    ]
  }
];let question = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'console.log()' statement in JavaScript?",
    answer: "To print output to the console",
    options: [
      "To declare a variable",
      "To create a loop",
      "To print output to the console",
      "To define a function"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which programming language is known for its use in web development and can be run in the browser?",
    answer: "JavaScript",
    options: [
      "Java",
      "C++",
      "Python",
      "JavaScript"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",
    options: [
      "Counter Style Sheets",
      "Computer Style Sheets",
      "Colorful Style Sheets",
      "Cascading Style Sheets"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the role of 'DOCTYPE' declaration in HTML?",
    answer: "To specify the version of HTML",
    options: [
      "To create a new document",
      "To specify the version of HTML",
      "To link external stylesheets",
      "To define a doctype"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In programming, what does the term 'variable' refer to?",
    answer: "A container for storing data values",
    options: [
      "A mathematical operation",
      "A conditional statement",
      "A container for storing data values",
      "A loop structure"
    ]
  }
];